fbuds.com 2015-03-29

# Privacy Policy

This site is owned and operated by Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. Your privacy and ours on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. We want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. 

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it. 

**1\. Information Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. gathers and tracks.** Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. gathers two types of information about users: 

1.1. Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our message boards or forums, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys. 

1.2. Information Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to members' needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. does not divulge any information about individual users to a third party. 

Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. gathers user information in the following processes: 

**2\. Optional Voluntary Information.** We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users: 

2.1. Message boards/forums. Users of the site's Message Boards and Forums must be registered members (both are free of charge) in order to post messages and to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password and email address. 

2.2. Polling. We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users. 

2.3. Surveys. Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party. 

**3\. Children.** Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. 

**4\. Usage Tracking.** Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).  
Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. 

**5\. Cookies.** We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Fbuds uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.  
You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. 

**6\. Use of Information.** Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.  
As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards, and forums. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas we do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.  
Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because we don't track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser or sponsor will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. 

**7\. Sharing of the Information.** Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keeping our service free. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. 

**8\. Security.** Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. 

**9\. Opt-Out Policy.** We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:   
\- opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters;   
\- opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users. 

**10\. Your Consent.** By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Sharyland Internet Partners, Inc. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
